ROMAN BELOVOLOV

WEB DEVELOPER

Location: Auckland City, New Zealand

Phone: 020 4471047

Email: belovolovri@gmail.com

Portfolio: https://belovolov.github.io

LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/roman-belovolov/

ABOUT ME

I am an experienced software developer with the emphasis on web applications. I possess a deep understanding of programing concepts and algorithms, as well as fundamental aspects of Internet and network protocols. I am also qualified in information security and write code and design systems with security in mind. I am responsible, reliable, deepthinking and constantly self-developing (see references)

SKILLS

Front-end React Redux HTML CSS3 Gulp NPM Git Webpack D3.js

Languages: Javascript Python C# PHP SQL

Back-end: Node.js Express.js ASP.NET Core Flask MongoDB MySQL

Cloud platforms: AWS Google Cloud Heroku

Unit testing: Mocha Chai

Industry Software development Information security Payment systems Machine Learning IoT

Knowledge: Networks Web Development (MVC, SPA, RESTful API)

EXPERIENCE

Back-end PEER ASSESS PRO LIMITED

developer/architect AUCKLAND

> Jul 2018 - present Transferring functionality of Google Forms and Google Sheets -based application to a separate (2 months)

product. I play roles of a system architect and a back-end developer. I work in a team with a front-

end developer, a UX/UI designer, and a product owner.

UNITEC INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY Full-stack web

developer/researcher **AUCKLAND**

> Full stack web-development on Javascript with React and Node.js. Sep 2017 - present

> > (1 year) Initially developed a JSON/CSV API for the Unitec's Auckland air quality project.

> > > Currently working on food & environment traceability research project.

Leading technical **CENTRAL BANK OF RUSSIA**

engineer

MOSCOW

Nov 2013 - Jun 2017

(3 years 8 months)

Work primarily included:

• technical support (tiers 2-3) of a multi-component payment system along with additional automated systems;

• deployment of testing environments, stress tests;

· automation of work tasks by scripting and programming;

FORMULASTROYPROYEKT System integrator/

administrator

MOSCOW

Aug 2015 - Sep 2015

(2 months)

Developed, set up and documented the IT-infrastructure of an office with 30 employees, then delegated the administration. Infrastructure included Active Directory, SMB file share, IP-PBX(Asterisk), dual-WAN in active-passive mode, Wi-Fi, client-server antivirus, VPN (testimony

available on request)

EDUCATION

2017 - 2018 Graduate Diploma in Computing

UNITEC INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY

AUCKLAND

Majoring in Software Development I took courses in Web Development, Databases, Machine Learning,

IoT, GUI programming

2009 - 2014 Specialist Diploma in Information security

NATIONAL RESEARCH NUCLEAR UNIVERSITY "MEPHI"

MOSCOW

Among subjects were: Network security, Application security, Cryptography, Programming, Algorithms

ADDITIONAL EDUCATION

I learned a lot of practical programming on FreeCodeCamp and Udemy courses, such as "ES6 Javascript: The Complete Developer's Guide", "The Advanced Web Developer Bootcamp", "Node with React: Full stack Web Development", "Git a Web Developer Job: Mastering the Modern Workflow" and others.

REFERENCES

Available upon request